1800gotjunk.com 2017-06-12

# Terms of Use and Privacy Policy 1-800-GOT-JUNK? LLC and RBDS Rubbish Boys Disposal Service Inc

Thank you for visiting the 1-800-GOT-JUNK? website (the "Site").  **PLEASE CAREFULLY REVIEW THE TERMS OF USE OF THE SITE AND THE PRIVACY POLICY.  **Since your use of the Site will indicate your acceptance of these terms, do not use the Site if you do not agree to be bound by these terms. We may periodically change the terms in our sole discretion and without notice so please check these terms from time to time since your continued use of the Site signifies your acceptance of any changed terms. These terms incorporate and include our Privacy Policy, outlined below, and any other guidelines or disclaimers that may be posted on the Site.

**USE OF THE SITE AND INDEMNITY**

You acknowledge that your use of the Site and of any information contained on the Site is for lawful informational and estimate or service booking purposes only. You agree you will not distribute, publish, transmit, modify, display or create derivative works from, or exploit the contents of the Site in any way without our express consent. You agree to indemnify, defend and hold harmless RBDS Rubbish Boys Disposal Service Inc. d.b.a. 1-800-GOT-JUNK? and its directors, officers, employees, franchisees, and affiliates from and against all liability and costs (including attorney fees) incurred in connection with, relating to or arising out of your breach of these terms, your unauthorized use of material on the Site, or your use of the Site. You acknowledge that the unauthorized use of the contents of the Site could cause irreparable harm to the 1-800-GOT-JUNK? brand and that in the event of an unauthorized use, RBDS Rubbish Boys Disposal Service Inc. d.b.a. 1-800-GOT-JUNK? and its directors, officers, employees, franchisees, and affiliates, as the case may be, shall be entitled to an injunction in addition to any other remedies available at law or in equity. You agree to cooperate fully as reasonably required in the defense of any claim. We reserve the right to assume the exclusive defence and control of any matter subject to indemnification by you.

**FEEDBACK AND SUBMISSIONS**

If you submit any material to or for use on the Site, unless all parties agree otherwise, you thereby grant RBDS Rubbish Boys Disposal Service Inc. d.b.a. 1-800-GOT-JUNK? and its franchisees and affiliates a nonexclusive, royalty-free, perpetual, irrevocable, and fully sublicensable right to use, reproduce, modify, adapt, publish, translate, create derivative works from, distribute, and display such content throughout the world in any media. You further thereby grant RBDS Rubbish Boys Disposal Service Inc. d.b.a. 1-800-GOT-JUNK? and its affiliates and sublicensees the right to use the name that you submit in connection with such content. By submitting material, you represent and warrant that you own or otherwise control all of the rights to the content that you post, that the content is accurate, that use of the content you supply does not violate the Site’s Privacy Policy, outlined below, and will not cause injury to any person or entity, and that you will indemnify RBDS Rubbish Boys Disposal Service Inc. d.b.a. 1-800-GOT-JUNK? and its directors, officers, employees, franchisees and affiliates for any losses incurred in relation to any claims resulting from content you supply. We have the right, but not the obligation, to monitor and edit or remove any activity or content from the Site. We take no responsibility and assume no liability for any content posted by you or any other third party on the Site.

**TERMINATION OF USE**

If you breach any provision of this agreement, you may no longer use the Site. We may, at any time and for any reason, suspend, modify, limit or restrict your access, temporarily or permanently, to some or all of the Site, without notice. Despite any termination of this agreement, we may continue to use your personal information in accordance with our Privacy Policy, outlined below.

**Ownership of the Site,  ** **COPYRIGHT AND TRADEMARK**

© 2013 RBDS Rubbish Boys Disposal Service Inc. All rights reserved. Unless otherwise noted, all materials on the Site are protected as the copyrights, trade dress, trademarks and, or alternatively, other intellectual properties owned by RBDS Rubbish Boys Disposal Service Inc. d.b.a. 1-800-GOT-JUNK?, its subsidiaries, its affiliates and others, and is protected by Canadian, American and international copyright, trademark and other laws. Your use of the Site does not transfer to you any ownership or other rights in the Site or its content.

**DISCLAIMER AND LIABILITY EXCLUSION**

RBDS RUBBISH BOYS DISPOSAL SERVICE INC. D.B.A. 1-800-GOT-JUNK? AND ITS DIRECTORS, OFFICERS, EMPLOYEES, FRANCHISEES AND AFFILIATES DO NOT ACCEPT ANY LIABILITY FOR YOUR USE OF THE SITE. YOUR USE OF THE SITE IS AT YOUR OWN RISK. THE SITE IS PROVIDED ON AN "AS IS" BASIS, WITHOUT ANY REPRESENTATIONS, WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED. RBDS RUBBISH BOYS DISPOSAL SERVICE INC. D.B.A.1-800-GOT-JUNK? AND ITS DIRECTORS, OFFICERS, EMPLOYEES, FRANCHISEES AND AFFILIATES WILL NOT UNDER ANY CIRCUMSTANCES BE LIABLE TO YOU OR ANY OTHER PERSON FOR ANY LOSS OR DAMAGE ARISING FROM, CONNECTED WITH, OR RELATING TO THE USE OF THE SITE BY YOU OR ANY OTHER PERSON.

**CHOICE OF LAW AND JURISDICTION**

This agreement is governed by the laws of British Columbia and the laws of Canada applicable in British Columbia. Any dispute arising from these terms shall be heard exclusively by the courts of the Province of British Columbia located in Vancouver.

**ENTIRE AGREEMENT**

This agreement, as modified from time to time, constitutes the entire agreement between you and us with respect to your use of the Site and supersedes any and all prior agreements with respect to your use of the Site.

**NO CONSENT OR WAIVER OF DEFAULT**

No consent or waiver by either party to or of any breach or default by the other party of its performance of its obligations under this agreement will be deemed or construed to be a consent to or waiver of a continuing breach or default or any other breach or default of those or any other obligations of that party. No consent or waiver will be effective unless in writing and signed by both parties.

**SUCCESSORS AND ASSIGNS**

The provisions of this agreement will enure to the benefit of and be binding upon each of RBDS Rubbish Boys Disposal Service Inc. d.b.a. 1-800-GOT-JUNK? and its affiliates, successors and assigns, and you and your heirs, executors, administrators, successors, permitted assigns, and personal representatives. We may assign this agreement and its rights and obligations under this Agreement without your consent.

## Privacy Policy

We are committed to maintaining your confidence and trust in all of our activities with you. Below is our Privacy Policy governing our use of information about you that you provide, actively or passively, while using the Site ("Information"). This Privacy Policy does not govern our collection of any information about you through any channel or by any method other than by your use of this Site. If you have any questions about this privacy statement or the content and practices of the Site, please feel free to contact us by clicking here.

**TRACKING TECHNOLOGY**

We collect non-personal Information about our website traffic and usage patterns from technology such as Cookies and Web Beacons. Cookies are small text files that help us to personalize the content of the Site. Web Beacons are electronic files used to track your navigation on a website or collection of sites, the completion of transactions, submittal of applications and browsing behavior.

We use cookies and other tracking technology to understand and save your preferences for future visits, to keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are permitted to use the information collected on our behalf to help us conduct and improve our business.

If you prefer, you can choose to turn off all cookies via your browser settings. However, if you turn your cookies off, some of our services may not function properly.

**ONLINE BEHAVIOURAL ADVERTISING**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit the Site. These companies may use information about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/>.

**INFORMATION WE COLLECT AUTOMATICALLY**

When you visit the Site, we collect some basic Information that does not identify individual users. This includes pages visited, types of products purchased, and feedback from our visitors, as well as location data, logs and other communication data, and information about your computer and internet connection, including your IP address, operating system and browser type.

Third party advertising companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other websites. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. These third party cookies do not collect personally identifiable information. For more information about cookies and how to opt out of third party data collection, please see the Tracking Technology section of this policy.

**INFORMATION YOU SPECIFICALLY PROVIDE**

We collect Information that you voluntarily provide when you register to access and use certain portions of the Site. We also collect information from you that is necessary to identify you and to process and fulfill your requests for information or service.

If you interact with our website by booking services, submitting feedback, joining a mailing list, or writing a review or comment you may provide us with information, including:

  * First and last name

  * Address

  * Email address

  * Phone number

**OUR USE OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION**

We use the Information in order to make the Site more useful and to respond to your queries, to inform users of new promotions, products and services offered by us, to improve our level of service, and to provide notifications regarding the Site and our products and services. We restrict access to your Information to those in our organization who require access in order to provide the Site, information and services to you. We also may share your Information with the following entities:

  * Our affiliated companies

  * Unaffiliated service providers with whom we may subcontract, including website hosting companies, fulfillment companies, payment processing companies, and other third party service providers

  * Government agencies and law enforcement officials, when required to do so to respond to subpoenas, court orders or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims

We also reserve the right to share Information with other organizations in the following situations, as authorized by law:

  * as permitted by law in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, violation of our intellectual property rights, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of the Site's Terms of Use or other agreements, or otherwise as required by law

  * when we have your consent to do so

  * when we need to share Information to provide any product or service you have requested

We also may use your IP address and information about the web pages you visit to gather broad demographic information, interests and behavior so that we may better understand our Site users. This Information may be used, for example, to analyze and improve our Site design and functionality.

We may also share your non-personal information to deliver tailored advertising to you that match your interests when you visit our Site as well as other websites.

You may opt-out of the use of your information. To learn more about the use of this information or to choose not to have this information used by our third-party advertising partner by opting out, please visit the Network Advertising Initiative by clicking [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).  **If you delete your Cookies, use a different browser, or buy a new computer, you will need to renew your opt-out choice.**

**FORMER USERS**

Even after you stop using the Site or your permission to use the Site is terminated or ends for any reason, we may continue to use the Information as provided in this Policy, as amended, and in accordance with applicable law.

**BUSINESS TRANSFER**

As we continue to develop, we might sell or buy the assets of similar companies. In such transactions, customer and user Information generally is one of the transferred business assets. Also, in the event that we or substantially all of our assets are acquired, such Information may be one of those transferred assets, and we reserve the right to buy or sell such assets.

**OPT-OUT POLICY**

When you provide Information via the Site and if you consent to us contacting you for this purpose, as required by law, we may use the Information to occasionally notify you about special promotional programs and other valuable services we offer. If you prefer that we not contact you in this manner, or want to withdraw your consent, we will promptly remove you from our distribution list at your request. Please send any such request to:

1-800-GOT-JUNK?  
Attention: Customer Experience  
301 – 887 Great Northern Way  
Vancouver, BC Canada V5T 4T5

You can also click [here](mailto:optout@1800gotjunk.com) or email us at [optout@1800gotjunk.com](mailto:optout@1800gotjunk.com) to email us your request, or you can call us at 1-800-468-5865.

**HOW TO REVIEW AND UPDATE YOUR INFORMATION**

You may e-mail us with changes to your information and contact preferences by clicking here.

**SECURITY**

We use a variety of standard protections to maintain the security of your online session. Although the Site has security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of Information under our control, we cannot guarantee that such security measures will be sufficient, will not be breached, and that your Information may not be disclosed or otherwise accessed in any unauthorized manner. Certain Information may be transmitted to you by electronic mail. Although it may be illegal to intercept or disclose these messages, these transmissions are not secured.

**CHILDREN'S PRIVACY PROTECTION**

The Site does not target children or provide products or services for use by children. We do not knowingly collect Information from persons under 18 years of age. If you are under 18 years of age, you may review the Site only with involvement of a parent or guardian, and you may not use any portion of the Site that would require collection of personal Information from you.

**LINKED INTERNET WEB SITES**

The Site may provide hypertext links to other websites that may contain privacy provisions that are different from those provided herein. We are not responsible for the collection, use or disclosure of information collected through those websites, and we expressly disclaim any and all liability related to such collection, use or disclosure. You are encouraged to read the privacy policies of other websites reached through the use of links from the Site.

**MODIFICATION**

As we grow and new features are added, or legal requirements change, this Privacy Policy may be modified. Any changes to the Site's Privacy Policy are effective as of the time they are posted on the Site. All Information submitted through the Site is subject to this Privacy Policy, as amended. This Privacy Policy was last updated in October 2013.

**HOW TO CONTACT US**

If you have any questions or complaints about our Site, our Privacy Policy, or the Information we collect, please contact our customer service team here.

© 2015 RBDS Rubbish Boys Disposal Service Inc. D.B.A 1-800-GOT-JUNK?. All rights reserved.
